alcurry98@gmail.com 917 613 6394

alcurry.com linkedin.com/in/alcurry github.com/AlCurry

IT Professional with expertise in development, systems support, and technical problem solving, experience resolving issues to users' satisfaction and working at client sites. Diverse development and bug-fixing skills. Available to travel or re-locate.

TECHNICAL SUMMARY

Programming Languages Scripting Operating Systems Databases Tools Javascript, C/C++, Java, J2EE, C#, SQL and Sybase stored procedures, tcl, Swift Korn, Bash & C Shell, Perl, PHP, DCL, HTML, CSS, Rexx Linux, several Unix flavors, VMS, Windows, IOS Sybase, Oracle, SQL Server, RMS, Firebase, MongoDb, mySQL Git, Xcode, Netbeans, Perforce, Eclipse, emacs, debuggers, IDEs, FIX Protocol, JSON

EDUCATION

George Washington University, Washington, D.C. Noble Desktop, New York, NY Pace University, New York, NY NYU Professional Studies, New York, NY University of New Hampshire, Durham, NH

Full Stack Web Development iOS App Development Red Hat Linux Systems Administration Intro through Advanced Java, C#/.NET, C++, Bash, Perl shell scripting. Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

RECENT PROJECTS

iOS app - PicDMC - December 2017

- · coded in Swift with Xcode
- in app store for iPhone & Ipad
- reverse geo-location, mapping, darksky weather API & settings
- App development class project Noble Desktop, Soho

Med-Trax - March 2018

- Javascript Node, Express, Handlebars
- FDA API, mySQL, passport, Sequelize, Bootstrap, and REST
- Deployed: med-trax.herokuapp.com
- One of 4 team projects at GWU Fullstack program

Online Portfolio - April 2018

- Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap
- Deployed: alcurry.com
- One of many solo projects at GWU Fullstack program
- Other projects: github.com/AlCurry

EXPERIENCE

Volunteer, New York, NY

October 2015 - present

Teaching assistant for Introduction to C++ at City University of New York
Technology tutor and Advisor at St. Charles Jubilee Senior Center and Eileen C. Dugan Amico Senior Centers

Systems Specialist, FIDESSA CORPORATION, New York, NY

March 2010 - July 2015

- Customized trading systems for major banks such as Bank of America, with some work at client sites in mid-town and in Brazil.
- Coded new features and fixes, with Java, bash, tcl, XML, and proprietary languages, on Solaris, Linux, and Windows.
- Automated loading of client data, synchronizing Sybase and an in-memory real time database, with Sybase SQL and scripting.
- Wrote requirements and system documentation of enhancements and fixes for clients, QA, UAT, and Operations.
- Resolved technical issues in both writing and verbally and addressed 2nd and 3rd level production support problems.

Sr. Software Developer, NYSE (formerly SIAC), New York, NY

December 1999 – April 2009

- Developed software for Amex Order File, order processing for Equities, Options, ETFs and Nasdaq, and associated systems.
- Responsible for a multi-screen database front end application allowing trading floor and operations various db access privileges.
- Coded in C, Java, scripting languages, Sybase SQL stored procs. Estimated enhancements, documented releases and test plans.
- Fixed numerous bugs in this older system, worked with QA as needed, assisted with weekend testing, and supported production.
- Contributed to major projects: Y2K, Decimalization, Trader Profile & auto-execution login, many new screens & executables.

Software Consultant, PROLIFICS, New York, NY

October 1998 - December 1999

- Automated code changes for software upgrades using Ksh, sed, awk scripts, fine-turning the results.
- Customized lengthy makefiles for C on various Unix flavors, compiling updated code with new libraries.
- Associated file management, manual and Y2K changes.
- Database work included Sybase and Oracle interfacing with C, both stored procedures and embedded SQL.
- Clients included Associated Press, AT&T, Lazard Freres, and the American Stock Exchange.